<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-12T11:15:07+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">new S pace</title><subtitle>We're students in Korea, Gyeonggi-do who want to access information about space easily.
</subtitle><author><name>Jihan</name><email>forcoding4@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">TEST DATA</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/12/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TEST DATA" /><published>2022-11-12T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-11-12T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/test</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/12/"><![CDATA[<p>Fancy grim again of nevermore the forgotten flown for i my, lord the what nothing the, from one metell whom and sorrow smiling my, and or your weak the sitting it quaint. Made the there nights more madam. Entrance discourse oh the or sent. Seeing distinctly aptly above ebony flirt shall soul gloating deep, quoth stock and what sought. Angels my nights rapping engaged napping but, dared suddenly to a spoke murmured only at ashore. Human a sitting no opened yet shore caught, whom followed door word made bust. Remember soul bust all more the, devil it burning sir bird some stood scarcely my, then from an its i or fiend a, quoth but ominous the there. Some evermore at a is bird ominous and at the, ghastly nevermore the on here floor truly heard a is. And leave upon broken linking was quoth seeming lie that, many door december the of this grave quaff angels no. Said you of heart doubting above other nevermore broken from, gaunt into then into more stood or from, enchanted grave shore or quaff more. Nights silken spoken soon in the core is upstarting i, i the he desert explore the while hath take. Be only my ungainly fiend has this thinking burned raven. Help stillness i sitting ebony nothing of fearing i or, louder wheeled lies bends thee whether bosoms clasp. Of scarcely is door quaint of this terrors the quaff. Uttered the grave mystery much soul lattice and in, not soul meaninglittle presently thy shadow no. Wheeled is morrow volume nevernevermore within leave placid ember with. My and books or stillness it my and of. Silken that upon the tinkled though not wished, me ease while came ominous. Tis such meant quoth surcease more lamplight you, whom betook youhere maiden the horror. Explore mien within sitting rustling word. Said a oer lattice a my yore wheeled in the, but is yore or cannot. Gileadtell hear of sitting thy or thy, volume door raven tis floor ember volume ember before. Dying have and still devil entrance in the. Sat quaint then there nevermore, of an raven disaster stood ghost sat but distinctly. Ominous scarcely door of an adore quoth weary the fowl. He is press leave flutter kind. Mefilled more chamber of upon of sculptured. Oer bird betook reclining memories flown from yore. Door was lie distant and i ebony, just entrance above and pallas raven its and unto, back books was morrow it upon the oer of angels, a each felt ever answer velvet and bosoms ember loneliness, have as whose burden within books eyes plainly or chamber. That stood now but radiant window to, i loneliness the and for peering. With ungainly sad at i perched that lamplight upon murmured. Lenore thee if we came nevermore. In a my in a and. Oh theeby said but my thing the though i, visiter it of no said silken, that the above nevermore bore fiend there implore eyes bore, from shall my and.</p>]]></content><author><name>Jihan</name><email>forcoding4@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy grim again of nevermore the forgotten flown for i my, lord the what nothing the, from one metell whom and sorrow smiling my, and or your weak the sitting it quaint. Made the there nights more madam. Entrance discourse oh the or sent. Seeing distinctly aptly above ebony flirt shall soul gloating deep, quoth stock and what sought. Angels my nights rapping engaged napping but, dared suddenly to a spoke murmured only at ashore. Human a sitting no opened yet shore caught, whom followed door word made bust. Remember soul bust all more the, devil it burning sir bird some stood scarcely my, then from an its i or fiend a, quoth but ominous the there. Some evermore at a is bird ominous and at the, ghastly nevermore the on here floor truly heard a is. And leave upon broken linking was quoth seeming lie that, many door december the of this grave quaff angels no. Said you of heart doubting above other nevermore broken from, gaunt into then into more stood or from, enchanted grave shore or quaff more. Nights silken spoken soon in the core is upstarting i, i the he desert explore the while hath take. Be only my ungainly fiend has this thinking burned raven. Help stillness i sitting ebony nothing of fearing i or, louder wheeled lies bends thee whether bosoms clasp. Of scarcely is door quaint of this terrors the quaff. Uttered the grave mystery much soul lattice and in, not soul meaninglittle presently thy shadow no. Wheeled is morrow volume nevernevermore within leave placid ember with. My and books or stillness it my and of. Silken that upon the tinkled though not wished, me ease while came ominous. Tis such meant quoth surcease more lamplight you, whom betook youhere maiden the horror. Explore mien within sitting rustling word. Said a oer lattice a my yore wheeled in the, but is yore or cannot. Gileadtell hear of sitting thy or thy, volume door raven tis floor ember volume ember before. Dying have and still devil entrance in the. Sat quaint then there nevermore, of an raven disaster stood ghost sat but distinctly. Ominous scarcely door of an adore quoth weary the fowl. He is press leave flutter kind. Mefilled more chamber of upon of sculptured. Oer bird betook reclining memories flown from yore. Door was lie distant and i ebony, just entrance above and pallas raven its and unto, back books was morrow it upon the oer of angels, a each felt ever answer velvet and bosoms ember loneliness, have as whose burden within books eyes plainly or chamber. That stood now but radiant window to, i loneliness the and for peering. With ungainly sad at i perched that lamplight upon murmured. Lenore thee if we came nevermore. In a my in a and. Oh theeby said but my thing the though i, visiter it of no said silken, that the above nevermore bore fiend there implore eyes bore, from shall my and.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">개기월식 및 천왕성 엄폐!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/07/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="개기월식 및 천왕성 엄폐!" /><published>2022-11-07T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-11-07T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/%EA%B0%9C%EA%B8%B0%EC%9B%94%EC%8B%9D-%EB%B0%8F-%EC%B2%9C%EC%99%95%EC%84%B1-%EC%97%84%ED%8F%90</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2022/11/07/"><![CDATA[<p>오늘 11월 8일, 앞으로 200년을 볼수 없는 진귀한 우주쇼가 펼쳐 진다고 한다. 바로 개기 월식과 천왕성 엄폐.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>개기월식은 8일 오후 6시10분부터 9시50분까지 총 3시간 40분 동안 개기월식이 진행된다. 개기월식과 동시에 8일 오후 8시 23분부터 9시 26분까지는 달이 천왕성을 가리는 천왕성 엄폐 관측이 가능하다. 엄폐는 멀리 있는 천체가 가까이 있는 천체에 의해 가려지는 현상을 말한다.
 <em>-동아일보</em></p>
</blockquote>]]></content><author><name>Jihan</name><email>forcoding4@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 11월 8일, 앞으로 200년을 볼수 없는 진귀한 우주쇼가 펼쳐 진다고 한다. 바로 개기 월식과 천왕성 엄폐. 개기월식은 8일 오후 6시10분부터 9시50분까지 총 3시간 40분 동안 개기월식이 진행된다. 개기월식과 동시에 8일 오후 8시 23분부터 9시 26분까지는 달이 천왕성을 가리는 천왕성 엄폐 관측이 가능하다. 엄폐는 멀리 있는 천체가 가까이 있는 천체에 의해 가려지는 현상을 말한다. -동아일보]]></summary></entry></feed>